<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Eric Hu&#39;s Blog</title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-02-27T04:40:23.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Eric Ju Hu</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pomodoro - UI Design</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2016/02/26/Pomodoro/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2016/02/26/Pomodoro/</id>
    <published>2016-02-27T03:28:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-02-27T04:40:23.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Last Winter, I decided to do something for myself. I have always been struggling with the issue of procrastination. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Last Winter, I decided to do something for myself. I have always been struggling with the issue of procrastination. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="iOS" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/iOS/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World!</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2016/02/26/hello_world/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2016/02/26/hello_world/</id>
    <published>2016-02-27T03:21:23.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-02-27T03:21:23.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thanks to hexo and github page, I finally had a personal blog to record down how I progressed through out learning and building things I like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am currently a undergraduate student at UCLA majoring in Mathematics of Computation. Though I had my first PC when I was eight, I haven’t had any experience with ‘serious’ programming until I took my first CS course at UCLA. It was challenging to me at first because the introductory courses were heavily theory based and I am the kind of person who like exploring and building new stuff rather than computing the dull and intimidating algorithms. (But I have to do that to get a job, sign.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I soon found my interest in mobile development, and in particular iOS development after the release of the new language, Swift. It is clear, simple and swifty (indeed as it is named). More importantly, by building apps, I get to brush up my designing skills. (I started painting since I was six but I merely practice it nowadays due to heavy schoolwork.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, I am building a task management app called &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ImEric/Pomodoro&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;external&quot;&gt;Pomodoro&lt;/a&gt;. And I plan to note down every progress I made or obstacles I encountered during the development of this app. Hopefully, it will get published and being appreciated by others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, world! I am here.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Thanks to hexo and github page, I finally had a personal blog to record down how I progressed through out learning and building things I 
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
